

WLADYSLAW ARTSIUKH

FRONTEND ENGINEER

CONTACT

- Poland, Lodz
- +48606940393
- workto22@gmail.com
- https://artyuhvladislav.github.io
- https://github.com/artyuhvladislav

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT TYPESCRIPT
REACT REDUX MONGODB
REST API GRAPHQL
NODE EXPRESS
WEBPACK HTML SASS CSS

LANGUAGE

POLISH A2

ENGLISH B2

RUSSIAN NATIVE

BELARUSIAN NATIVE

HOBBIES

Football Swimming
Gym Music



ABOUT ME

Hi my name is Wladyslaw Artsiukh. I am a frontend developer with knowledge of React.js. Love personal improving in IT. Theoretical skills in designing, developing, optimizing web-based applications. Strong interpersonal and communication skills, able to work under the pressure and handle multiple tasks. More about my experience, you can ask me personally.



EDUCATION

> BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

JUN 2012 - AUG 2018

Bachelor of Science: Geodesy and aerospace geotechnologies-2018

> RSSCHOOL

MAR 2020 - DEC 2020

Got practical experience and knowledge of: JavaScript

TypeScript Git, GitHub (clone, add, commit, push, pull, merge, rebase, working with Pull Request NPM, Webpack CSS3 / HTML5 Chrome DevTools, Figma Understanding of the REST

> ANDERSEN LAB

MAR 2020 - DEC 2021

Working with frontend and backend team on bank application (SPA).

I implemented UI and frontend logic using react and redux as a state managment.

Work communication by using jira agile scrum methodology.



EXPERIENCE

> FRONTEND ENGINEER, RICHNESS COMP.

AUG 2020 - FEB 2021

Built a full-stack web application to allow clients byuing woods. Used react to allow users to instantly update web UI without reloading. Used redux as a state managment. Kept tracking users bugs and fixed them. Tetsted react components using Jest.

Worked with:

JavaScript node/express
TypeScript Redux
React, REST API,
MongoDB, mongoose Axious,

> FRONTEND ENGINEER, FREELANCE

FEB 2021 - CURRENT

Built front-end applications with ReactJS. Components, pages, sorting, searching, pagination, filtering, popup windows, etc. Interacts with the backend, backend requests.

Design pages navigation without reloading. A global data stores for the entire applications. Strongly typed code in TypeScript. LocalStorage to store sites settings. Lazy Loading (lazy loading) + debounce (optimization for finding pizzas). Optimized components redraws/renders, code splitting (separating code into specific JS files), and JS file tracking.

Worked with:

JavaScriptRedux toolkitJestTypeScriptHTML5nodeReact,SCSSexpressReact-router v6REST API, axiospostman